hello yeah we live live voice all right
so to recap things that we've learned
the corona virus is just socks that's
something that we learned what else did
we learn that's all we learned no
actually if you look behind me you see
that I went to the supermarket and I
bought two weeks of food because I did
some I did some models this morning I
mean like really dumb stuff I kind of
just like did this and woke up so this
is the month of April and this is my
model is very very crude but this is the
number of people infected in America at
the current rate so as you can see
around like April 15th well so I did
this math and that I'm like damn I
should go to the supermarket so I went
to the supermarket because for this part
of the curve you're gonna want to keep
your doors locked and you're gonna want
to have a good source of food and water
here's when the m6 teams come out you
know the m16s we was talking about
but does this let you do any like I
haven't found a is there a good website
that lets you do like projection well
look we stopped the curled a virus in
its tracks
displayed comto
um doesn't look like a curve it's just
New York
hmm okay that's the first day it looks
like it's leveling off but you know that
can all be very very suspicious George
you look Jewish he's you on your team I
am circumcised and I do hear that that's
the most painful part of countries are
already hitting me max carrying capacity
okay well that's very optimistic with
you I think Italy is the highest at 0.1
if we look at the US that sure looks
like an exponential curve to me can i
zoom in on that you know we really try
to stay away from news and we try to
only focus on data I just downloaded I
downloaded this data from my god ball so
this is just this is the data as graphed
on days of March zero is actually the
last day of February so if you look at
that and you can say like okay that
doesn't look like a curve but not put
the log on that I mean it's pretty well
guys beautiful
it's a nice grass now but what I really
want to see is is projections there any
good websites that have projections yo
look into MSM and how it inhibits what's
this this is part of code of ours check
my Doc's here I'm having an l RP
I'm confused by this but ya know I just
I just downloaded this from from plague
calm and this is just the the number of
confirmed cases in the United States you
guys haven't seen play calm this is a
good way to watch this oh my god it's
even higher now 33 yeah forty three
point six it's the curve perfect thing
to do that's that's the real exponential
there
he's like 30 32 I'm 30
the interesting thing so
hospitalizations I wish I could just
filter out every news story doesn't tell
me what I want
12% have been hospitalized but it
doesn't matter that much what age you
are right for whether you get
hospitalized the ICU it starts to matter
a lot more if you're if you're older
they're a lot more likely to end up in
the ICU and you're a lot more likely to
uh to die I said a bench partly
Singapore well I mean those countries
are really I don't know what Singapore
did specifically but South Korea took
well not quite China's approach but um
you know they they tracked people's cell
phones I mean they they enabled the
Batman device like that's probably worth
it if our government was that confident
yeah patient medical data how can it be
possible that China all of a sudden
didn't report new cases let me show you
why China didn't report their cases
here's my theory about that I don't
think if you guys don't really care
codex I love this website it's got Alex
Lee is a genius
returning home with your disease will
not make your planned parents pleased
infecting mom and dad proves you have no
conscious those who don't report their
fever or class enemies hiding among the
people save pennies not wearing a mask
spend a fortune getting treatment on
your sick bed a surgical mask or a
breathing tube it's your call
right so I mean yeah China has known in
cases oh this is a nice data set
signing man that's my Wolfram ID
Oh sequence available whoa
borrowed noise we speak English in this
channel
I'm gonna refresh twice so I can see
that your account 321 all right cool I
think it's time to get started for
tonight it's first we need some tea
I like word as well all the CSV for that
date is at the bottom of the page just
something good to grab for later you
never know when you're gonna need data
well you know more people have died in
9/11 9/11 was was an attack on US soil
though and I think that's why so little
data
China was not behind the attack guys
though I mean it's interesting thinking
about China originally really downplayed
this and then they went they did like a
complete 180 from downplaying it to you
know those propaganda posters but I
think this is what you get if you
actually get a smart government that
cares most of all about economic growth
and this isn't necessarily the wrong
choice you know people in America are
always like but you got to think of the
people's lives the economy be damned I
mean if we're using the excess economy
growth for you know bullshit maybe this
is true but the standard of living in
China has risen so rapidly
China has pulled more people out of
global poverty in the last 30 years
through their economic growth than any
other country you know China was it was
a 30 years ago maybe maybe 40 years ago
right 40 years ago Shenzhen was a
fishing village now Shenzhen is a 20
million person crazy city with some of
the sickest malls in life up next I've
never been to India and maybe I'll
change my mind if I go but tel believe
it when I see it what did someone that
lost their job do online to make one
capitalist utopia and communist dreams
tape who thinks a communist state is a
dream state I don't know what kind of
dreams you're havin all right let's get
back to work other remember that thing
that I like lost I found it again this
here down here so these are those
this is what we're looking at this is
the coronavirus I mean it's nice because
this one breaks down or one a/b
anarcho-communism yo I want a date once
and this girl told her she's an
anarchist and I was like that's
interesting so I went back to my car and
I got my gun out of the glove
compartment and I put it in her face and
I told her you're my slave and this
worked you know for about two minutes
until the bartender pulls out a shotgun
he said you know what you guys are both
my slaves and this worked for about ten
minutes until the army showed up outside
with some tanks
pointing them at the barn if you are all
my slaves and then what kind of back to
you know where we started so that's what
I think of an army
yeah military this oak / - github IO has
projections so sighs oh thank you for
subscribing I know that girl was kind of
weird she brought our dog to the bar oh
projections now we're talking
wait can I project further wait but I
want to go further can I not go further
[Music]
how do I project
everybody for the last couple weeks it's
been very logarithmic when I think about
how it Aaliyah stand handling this story
and you guys kept asking me the question
like when is this all going to be over
when is this all going to be over and I
was just like I don't know you know when
I started these streams I didn't take
coronavirus very seriously and now that
I've learned that well it's you know
SARS I've taken a little bit more
seriously Oh is there any way to go
further with the projection is this
probably open source
No
is the source of this summer
let me go out further what does
ah there we go mad
can I predict more
this is a cool source code
yes -
some social shame is responsible biased
as science is this what the people can't
handle the truth
probably all cool things to learn about
there's only like incredible Python
packages out there now that's models I
don't know why my donation never showed
up didn't check but I don't think the
wallet I have on my phone supports seg
would address us it's the Bitcoin cash
wallet they have the private key you
know I have the private key little cold
steal his crypto I got like 600 bucks
social blocks has been extended in the
Netherlands
yeah the 20 was fucking gone
what is this doing historical reply
we're getting distracted I promise we'll
get to reverse engineering it a little
bit what is this doing
Oh Python package show molecular
dynamics simulations now we're talking
MD analysis that'll work that is where
we were gonna go well I said as cool
that I found it we did say we were gonna
try some molecular dynamics today let
that run for a bit maybe it'll
eventually do something all right
don't ask me how I studied to code don't
ask me about why we got banned from desk
or a school I will say this the people
that you know with flu symptoms probably
have the flu the flu affects millions of
people every year the flu didn't stop
just because there's coronavirus you
know the amount of people who a little
bit sick now and probably like I'm sure
I have the corona virus I'm sure I have
it well I mean do you have because it
came with the Mac
[Music]
alright guys let me show you what you
bought oh I got crackers stuff today
check out what's in these bags check out
some these bags no one knows where I
left a couple weeks that one's gonna be
China trying to rob me of these potatoes
yeah now I'm ready for the m-16 man
testing my lockout I can use the potato
skins is TP I have no idea why people
are buying I bought two weeks of food
and I'm gonna start eating it now doing
the prediction data
Wow these people went really overboard
with like this this model seems way too
complicated that seems like it runs too
slowly when like just fitting a line to
the log it'd probably be pretty good
no okay make figures if you guys want to
see me do this how do you want to get
back to reverse engineer you guys can
vote with my comments what is it yes me
reverse yes isn't doing what I'm doing
out on all the votes seems 50/50 or
should we make macaroni and cheese
macaroni and cheese and hot
oh sweet United States number fun I like
didn't go out
we're going to spend a few minutes
trying to fix this and if we can't fix
it we can fix it
we just want a model for the United
States that extends coronavirus to come
out well this is already beautiful
Ashley you know they used to have a name
for it used to be called czars
so this is SARS detail
does this have the predictions or does
it need that stuff that I commented out
sweet it has predictions
[Music]
let's go into the modeling protection
don't show predictions more than ten
days ago I make the prediction longer
weird immunities like the biggest
crowdsource maybe this is it yeah
production tanks do posterity there
just didn't actually work at all still
is calling historical replay with us so
that thing that was actually taking
forever Ron I think it was running on
every country and that's why I was
taking so long but we of course only
care about America so if we just make it
work for America I'm happy stupid I
already writes the stuff I don't know if
it rewrites it again
well so history alia now I know we leave
America here you can you can follow my
instructions as you can do for Shyam if
we want to know if we want to know when
is the shit hits the fan date this is
irresponsible graph making oh oh yeah so
I think there's a problem I think we
can't even see it I'm gonna log
yeah all right
so yeah
doesn't automatically scale at some
point anymore
sweet okay so we're here now oh this is
this is perfect this is exactly what I
was looking for
so yeah we're we're here right now and
if we continue on the current trajectory
we'll hit a million cases in about two
weeks and we'll hit a hundred million
cases about two weeks after that it's
March 23rd
what's April 23rd yeah April 23rd we now
and this is of course going off with
confirmed cases it seems like 50% of
people don't have symptoms Society was
nice while it lasted the three blue one
brown video is very good I've been
against the graph so you're gonna reach
some point so it's interesting also that
we have the social isolation and we
don't see this at all we don't see it
reflected anywhere
[Applause]
who's getting arrested for spreading
rumors
oh yeah well that was a sham this is
America you cannot say we're not we're
not we're isn't hearing yet we're just
extrapolating out
so we'll say um the I think the
population with the highest penetration
right now is Italy's and it's at 0.1%
0.1% of America would be 300 million
three hundred thousand people so yeah
you know what if we hit a million people
by April 5th everybody run for shelter
don't run for shelter calmly walk and
shelter in place for the next two weeks
can we see the Italy graphic I think
should work so some of Italy's effects
appear to have been working I mean yeah
the United States will pass Italy at
some point
so it's this is just active cases I mean
the United States will obviously pass a
delay at some point because Italy has 60
million people and we have 300 the
question really is what percent of the
population gets this disease I think the
best way to estimate this what for some
of the Golden Princess cruise ship
number of cases Diamond Princess I get
real data that's not news can someone
find that the cruise ship data I mean
yeah the cruise ships recycle da or that
you know what kind of all on a cruise
ship right yo it must be terrible okay
you get three free Carnival Cruises
oh this one we really were trying to do
site sweet picnic girl returns new sites
as well which is kind of upsetting okay
but god this is whenever I look at these
decentralized and projects it's like
this is terrible just terrible I don't
want to have to pick one of these I
don't know what any of these things
stand for why don't you start with that
I get that it respects my privacy and
all I don't care
anybody who wants can see my searches
the only thing is I don't want shitty
news great okay cruise ships this is a
tale from the CDC okay ah yeah it's nice
this think is a fake or is it really
live yeah I've seen the New York Times
one
what do you mean is it fake fake what do
you think it's fake
okay
so the Diamond Princess cruise ship had
dirty I mean this is simple math now
that's just let's just look at
percentages right so assume that like
the cruise ship fully circulated the air
and there were seven hundred eleven
cases and I've heard that half of them
were asymptomatic twenty percent so
about if we assume that they're not
testing people without symptoms then ten
percent of people look like they're
gonna get the disease assuming that this
stuff doesn't work
so 10% of America is 30 million okay
well I don't take the noise tank on
anything to do with me yesterday
so 300k dead if you're going with a 10%
mortality which seems high and not know
not for educate with their virus it
seems like 3 million with divine well so
6 million with nama 60 million with the
virus 30 million that shows symptoms and
then of those seems like 5% death rates
about 5% if you're going off the SARS
second million people well I don't think
the Holocaust was faked
we're gonna put on a lovely song and
then we're gonna get to her first
engineer
you
you don't like the music billion
bitcoins well you know good thing this
stream is not democracy what are y'all
mucuna decide everyone should switch to
pi torch
yeah it seems right so basically yeah I
mean this year just um everyone's yeah
sometime I let the people phone so they
think it's a democracy kind of like
bright eyes right
no I think Jonathan's right but exactly
it's like a real democracy most Fraga to
understands what's up
[Music]
when it'll return you mean immortal
technique if you guys really want a
mindful dance with the devil all right
let's get back into this with a little
bit of just improving our documentation
so for reference the issue that we're
working on you can find them here to
read me Oh actually so we have two open
questions how is or one a be cleaved
into polypeptides can we predict this in
the sequence let's look into that
question of that and the other question
we're gonna look into is which protein
is the immune system responding to
you know you think 20 percent it's not
right as the upper bound for infection
the city's you have got quite nice graph
right like I mean it's starting to taper
off I don't know maybe the upper bound
is a little bit higher if someone loose
the repo especially if you subscribes so
one and a half American is dead I think
that's a pessimistic
[Music]
ma'am
no it's possible
we're gonna see we're gonna find out in
the next few weeks whether he did like
no I think or fizz cleaner I think we're
gonna find out in the next couple weeks
how well the like the social distancing
stuff is working out we're gonna get
lots of really cool experiments across
all the countries no and we're not at
the forefront is Italy right now is at
0.1% but really it is interesting
someone did link that Italy data saying
that it's going down is plague calm
open-source because I would love to
submit a pull request to be able to
switch this to graft to log mode cuz
like you can't see anything unless it's
in log mode we have my viewer I have the
New York Times one is good
making my computer lag okay this is
making my computer lag
this is cool I'll check it out later
what i'm not streaming I just don't have
my and I saw this weekend look at Italy
Italy actually does appear to be
tapering off even if we go out further
well
I mean yeah it's really not taking into
account the second-order effects this is
also only active cases so 1% of Italy is
600,000 yeah I haven't even talked about
case fatality rates I just don't really
know I mean it depends on so many
factors you know when you look at when
you look at when you look at Germany you
know like how does Germany not have any
deaths I mean they don't have that many
recovered either so maybe they're just
early like they don't seem that much
earlier don't like Spain which has like
20 exits but oh now I'm heavy into
speculation realm we're done with that
for now
stop saying racist stuff Ben Jay I don't
tolerate any racism around here this is
a no racism place no racism that's right
that's right
okay I don't want to let this turn into
a general coronavirus speculation
discussion I will just say I bought two
weeks food this morning I recommend
everyone else do this thing because work
day still have lots of macaroni and
cheese to eat if you don't have two
weeks of food in your house already it's
the kind of thing that I could be more
serious about
man I just did the math on calories all
right okay we can check this out too so
this is not that bad
the first milder outbreak protected
against the SARS
back fitting data okay so the cleaving I
think that the cleaving is happening
with these proteinases
former NSP one served domains
popping like protease there's good stuff
on this website so it's this responsible
for the cleavage located at the end
terminus of the replica poly protein so
the replicates poly protein is or flow
1a and or flow 1b
participates together with NSP for
let's understand what happiness
[Music]
so I was listening system before I saw
the hacker days I forgot what it was
called yeah yeah this guy he just played
your eyes chiptunes yeah
[Music]
let's look into molecular dynamics while
we listen to this because we can't think
[Music]
I wonder what stopped the parents I
listened to that in high school it's
kind of shifted open my eyes thank you
for subscribing
[Music]
oh you want a song my underwear goes
inside the pants I will listen to it on
streem I know I know what other songs
kind of like it what's it called oh I
can't even think of a guy
nomads know it's it's an old Portland
guy nomads and it's it's it's a
classical piano beat
we're gonna find this now because it's
gonna drive it crazy if we don't
actually if we go to my YouTube
I used the I liked it so much that I use
the easy song and mess yeah pick me
apart yeah
[Music]
species
these boys just to tell me my purpose is
worthless
[Music]
somebody stole my car radio and now I
just sit in silence also most of it's
terrible but other side by Macklemore
defenses remix shit got me into sipping
mean man you know I listen to that I'm
like damn sibling that's a little Bogart
of us yeah I never really switched up
the black art
[Music]
now us so much
20,000 atoms all right wait there was a
network there what does mr. Nolan my
twitch push down this is the github for
play calm oh you want to add a log graph
to this we didn't like do them a favor
did somebody do it
whoa this is so cool
I mean I just love to be able to is
there already a way that I just don't
know I want this on lock
we can do is confirmed daily increase
yesyes that's the only fault yeah that's
really good
why they took log mode out why did they
get rid of lock does someone want to
read The Changeling to figure out why
they get rid of oh you stepped Chinese
and separate there I'm gonna be that an
oversight with playing with molecular
dynamics tools well so you see notice
how it's it and the analysis is an
object-oriented library to analyze
trajectories from MD and now from
molecular dynamics simulations but the
question is okay now how do I actually
trigger a molecular dynamics simulation
like what do I use for that
you know the number of real trajectories
for test grow max collagen machine it's
one of these things that's gonna need
like huge amounts of computers like a
big cluster the good news is I have a
big cluster
they got rid of log because they're
monitoring people visiting the site that
doesn't make sense
well we back on the hype train y'all the
high trains back yo I love the high
train it made me money yesterday this is
what I vlog I'm gonna have a log scale I
see that's much better
[Music]
hmm all right things look pretty good
for Italy right now but we're done with
us we're getting distracted
we're only all about that hype train
right now croco thank you well at the
level 2 hype train we got a hundred
percent I think we're about to get to
the level 3 hype train choo choo uh how
to lecture for MD analysis I'll say is
it long
yo level 3 hypetrain
we got we got four minutes to get some
more subs no they've got any more noise
complaints someone yelling we're gonna
watch this later
it looks like Gro max is the thing to
use we have excellent kuda thanks GPU
acceleration Wow
let me show you something I have
we got a lot of those machines Akama
choo-choo
thank you for the hundred bits Nashua
Valene National Boyd avoider
yo anyone else who subscribes right now
you get a shout out you got three
minutes I'll give you a shout-out we're
gonna go back know the claims are all
fake we learned
Kuroko thank you for the bits thank you
for the bits trocol keeping those bits
coming yeah I love it
love it look at them GPUs man we got
plenty of GPUs to fire off and grow max
is this a tutorial for this NAMD is this
a different one
what is this solvating the protein to
having a protein structure file all gems
for you thank you
71% we got two minutes to get the hype
train to level four and then we can give
up on the hype chain if you would
thinking of subscribing right now's the
time right now is the time to subscribe
grow max how do we put things in to grow
max Globex looks better than this one I
trust this one last I mean
why do I need a protein structure file I
guess okay fine it doesn't actually fold
the proteins mr. zlz thank you for
subscribing Gold sees thank you for
subscribing Gold skis where I train
level 4 it's so light it's gotta be
someone just using grow max
illya RPV thank you for subscribing can
we study protein folding through
molecular dynamics and simulation
okay so I'm Tasso this is what this is
what the guys talked about using what
that Zang website talked about using
what do I think of using email written
next to thank you for that for the bits
first in or a structural some templates
oh it is Zhang lab yeah this is actually
the thing that they make and they're the
ones who have that who had that analysis
of the yeah the coronavirus here over
here and they generated these models see
hmm I fixed the estimated TM score and I
guess if the way I test it works is it
identifies yeah structural templates
with low mats you know but I'll just
love to name things like this
you see the Stanford paper about my
programming challenge No
do you think the US is gonna develop an
app look at that time they tried to make
the health care website
some of my eyebrow
is there way to see where the virus
overlaps with a bat yeah we could do
that actually have a link for that in
the
this doesn't mean it's okay
like what that's I mean I don't know if
I got a a submission of their their
their test results if they submit their
test results to me I'll tell them how
they did okay this doesn't work at all
you can't randomly shuffle the pairs of
data and take 20% put 80% of in the
training set and 20% of in a test set
the reason why is those frames that you
randomly pulled out are extremely
correlated with the frames and the
training set that looked just like it
see what I'm saying you can't do that
level three high training share choo
choo hype y'all look at that yeah you
can't do that
how do they know well it's just this
boom all right back to read me how do
researchers usually hear those dogs
does not indicate snakes
by the way I feel like I did read the
comments and someone said I got the
number of base pairs of HIV wrong whoa
really
HIV is you can fit three H IVs in one
coronavirus look at this paper for how
the researchers know okay
I'll put this link in here don't you do
it mark town right
it took four by two viral system and I
think I saw the other one in there too
yeah
so 4 3 + or 5 or cleaving it's very cool
part is important targets for the
development of a new just if you prevent
the cleaving or that's clever
you Chicago where fun goes to die I
believe in that school it doesn't matter
if it's ours her oh I believe in it even
more if it's about SARS ok a lot of the
science that's come out about
coronavirus I think is kind of crap
because you know
one of your popular stream coronavirus
stuff yeah right
oh okay look you see I think that in
SARS they're calling at different things
you just check here
I'm checking me in the in this structure
because I might want to change my naming
to match
nc spel so they're calling this 113 you
might want to change my naming and CSP
10 wears so that's 12
where is Oh 11 is like hidden down there
okay 13 amino acids just to make my
numbering match the other people's
Tom using their language 1308
that's ten
someone found out that I put two 7s in
the Czar's they submit a pull request
boy it's pretty funny my type seven
twice okay now my my stuff matches their
frameshift we learned a little bit about
these
Oh
which numbers which
I can't be right
what are those locations mean those just
can't be right because some are do you
like 12k and a virus
you know zoom in too much no
yeah it's like right around where I'm at
that missing point pump this link
computing the opening of that despite
all about this yes there's yeah there's
two
sorry to spike in motion
yeah look at that
would it be used to this yeah oh wow
they they have it cool we modified the
bond orders and the sugars we use the a
raft oh I see what they did so they
didn't like this isn't like molecular
dynamics or anything they just maybe you
can download both the proteins actually
have them both both here see any of the
open stay in the close date so they just
build something to to go between them
wait hang on I got a I gotta do
something for work I'm just gonna do it
right over here so you guys can't see it
I'm sorry you know what it's not secret
what's your question
if someone will link me the graph would
use to see the US numbers um so I
modified this Cova dashboard thing I
could just search The Cove it - but it's
probably good the best accuracy on the
comet and I test set so get the virus
stay home
I mean there's an argument to be made
that if you're gonna get it you want to
get it right now
before you know all the hospitals are
really overloaded
you had to get like a month ago that was
really the time to get it
imagine how good the people recovered
from well a chance of that out community
guitars
sorry specific IgG antibody I've seen
this like reference before I don't
really know what it is
immunoglobulin G whoa I mean it's just
like a what's the DNA sequence of this
thing
I mean base-pairs is this thing
look so
I don't know a heavy constant gamma one
is no I don't think this is right let's
not get too distracted three full-text
how do I get three full text take this I
go to sign up combat TW put that in
there you're free text
is it a bad time to eat meat no top
right of puppet oh sweet
despite protein and the nuclear caps
approached me and they spelled nucleo
capsid home concerns me contribute to
only the antibody production oh ok I
mean that that kind of gets it like one
of those questions that we were we were
asking let's just do a citation here
spell it right not just oh they actually
write a tiny documentation for this an
sp3 and MSP father know it is what they
were saying right uses the 3 CL Pro
which is n SP 5 and a Pappy like
protease which is n sp3 it's interesting
the like the way that it's cut up is
actually inside of the protein
contribute dominantly the antibody
production during the cost of the
disease spiked protein especially the
ACE to binding region it's capable of
producing neutralizing antibody 5 major
they spell nucleo capsid are wrong there
too
it is a Chinese Journal so you know
the pattern of cytokines are all these
people going back and reading the SARS
papers because these papers are so much
better than any of the coronavirus
papers I've read
what's this one
what is this
they tested the biologists
the survey was negative against all of
them except for one guy who got bitten
by a bat I don't know about cytokines so
I mean you know they always talk about a
cytokine storm and that's what Hydra
yeah this this is that they gave us in
France because they think it prevents
the cytokine storms
is there good video like is there one of
these that's not like at a stupid high
level retaining system of pathogens and
other fourth don'ts each integer has a
unique oh this is no no no no no so is
that good one of these can someone find
a good how the immune system actually
works that mentions like lymphocytes and
cytokines and stuff
viruses become more transmissible and
less deadly well there's I'm role locked
into clique is this is this a rick roll
link this is too long i won't like one
of those new youtubers like you know
like like Wendover and stuff like those
people who make those really good
explaining videos that coronavirus
explained he video was very good
it's the right of when I clicked before
[Music]
a pathogen is a disease causing
organisms a few examples which will be
on the screen
anybody's very well-equipped to try to
deal with the fact it does get in it
we're gonna discuss this in the context
of some of the blood cells that are
involved red blood cells they are they
for transporting oxygen they're also the
NIP recites kind of phagocytes the
protective factors like the both types
of white blood cells
if we look what they me do it like here
in is much T lymphocytes cytokines are
messenger proteins you can see first of
all this red blood cell to find out if
one of them yet that's one we can see
hundreds of them on the street
the lymphocyte there you can tell it
that the liver said because it's got
that really large nucleus and the
fungicide out here can distinguish that
from the lymphocyte because of the
unusual shape opportunities and we
describe this is have lured people use
it how about chickens need to fit in the
inside of a building or later those
lymphocytes when a pathogen enter the
body it has something on its cause and
two Jet's and these antigens can be
recognized by the antibodies of the
right type of lymphocyte it produces
these antibodies in large numbers and
when they attach to the antigen that
results in the destruction of this
packaging well how exactly did it work
well there's a few different methods
that antibodies can use in order to
destroy packaging first of all they
might cause this certain set of
reactions which is gonna result in the
cell membrane of the positive into the
open another thing that might do is
might make it easier for phagocytes to
find the proper general discourse
talking about how the phagocytes kind of
story positive another thing you can do
is in make the pathogens to stick
together which again makes it easier for
pathogens to find them and above them
but also every letter from all about its
its deal business imagine you and a
bunch of your friends all stuck together
you find it really difficult to have
your lunch and things like that it's a
wonder realize that very specific
antibodies are needed for specific
religions and since each lymphocyte
makes only one type of antibody am i
took like a why don't we want to find
the probability of site they can produce
the record bodies to destroy the
packaging and the consequences you might
get sick in the meantime before you
already actually find the correct
antibody and is able to destroy that
pathogen
one thing that happens is that memory
cells of that leukocytes are produced
after fighting the infection
so the copies are the specific with
recycle needs to sit there copies
ordinary cells and what that means is if
that pathogen Nebuchadnezzar before you
get it it could immediately start
producing the only bodies that it needs
and then it can fight off the package
and before that time to make you sick so
it's an inequality at City not sympathy
to the second time this is immunity
let's look at the next type of white
blood cell and these are fighters like
to live at a very great different method
of destroying packages first of all the
pathogen enters the body and then the
fungicide recognizes it and starts to
move toward it then the thing that comes
is the phagocytes engulfs the pathogen
it's really important to use the correct
vocabulary here don't say that the
phagocyte it's a very different review
then what did inside of the front of
site it gets destroyed using enzymes and
finally the homeless broken-down product
of the of the pathogen are inserted from
the cell and then it's been destroyed
the the positivity destroying the far
side were born I didn't go for new cells
so whatever comes we'll examine
questions well one possible one is that
he might give you this sort of picture
truly good what might look like these
are red blood cells these are
lymphocytes and these are phagocytes
isn't given food to attack each other so
now this is a red blood cell and it's
used to carry oxygen throughout your
body this is a lymphocyte and it makes
antibodies but it only makes a specific
antibody and antibodies can do a whole
bunch of things it can get they needs to
stick together and this is phagocytes
don't say that they eat pathogens they
engulf them
oh you're responsible for transporting
oxygen via the lymphocyte and this
function is to produce antibodies to
help destroy pathogens and C is called a
photo site and you might be telling us
say something like at each puppet once
again
[Music]
sweet yo I'm gonna get a degree in bio
when I'm done with this why just listen
man you bad bro you mad you know what
bro I got a plan for you you should
start your own competing coronavirus
stream no that was a meme from yesterday
you guys okay
cytokines and T lymphocytes do user
these are the DS I've seen the stuff
from from from aids acquired
immunodeficiency syndrome is terrible
completely realtalk guys you can now buy
a test at home to test for AIDS and like
it's not like you mail it in it's like
you can just take it right there and you
like mix some stuff together create a
week share does not give you aids no and
the test is for HIV I should be specific
about that
AIDS is what HIV causes unless of course
you're carrying Mullis then you don't
believe that
Kary Mullis was the inventor of PCR you
won the Nobel Prize and then went on to
talk about
meliss express disagreement with the
scientific evidence supporting climate
change and ozone depletion already can
go either way on that the evidence that
HIV causes AIDS and then are then really
you know an asserts is belief in
astrology
why don't they link these together you
know I do always find that it's weird
someone mentioned the someone mentioned
that the Holocaust was a hoax a couple
comments back and like this very
obviously isn't true but I find it funny
that they're like they label like
denialists right like like whatever they
have to label the nihilists I always
wanted her it doesn't it feel a little
more skeptical yeah denialists right you
know there's no like you know two plus
two equals four denial essence though
you know I have a finite this guy's I
have a finite test so you can look up
what that means you know has some weird
shit that I believe in
so it seems like the igg1 is still
produced persist for a long time while
IgM is expressed transient way
whoa
immunological epitopes in the spike
protein so for reference you know guys
remember that this is the spike protein
here we should label it with the number
of base pairs or the number of amino
acids come here that's here
1273 amino acids and remember that it's
a trimer I think I'm using the right
word yeah just like three copies that
kind of leave together quality mean
grows
oh so that's in size v1 so they added
they added a bunch of what's a glycol I
sation site there's like a whole world
of bio words no no he didn't exactly
take that drug I think he I think the
guy who died took look it up a Z or Y 9
yes so the problem was he took chloro
quinine not hydrochloric y9 so it's
actually really not yeah hydroxy a less
toxic derivative of chloroquine
which one is it's called like yeah Black
Widow yeah you can and you can like buy
this like these people you have it you
can you can like pick it up in you go
down to Mexico and take that off
phospholipid bilayer we learned about
that what's the book of ours I can't I
can't not click that way
nice book bro
four regions with highly immune
reactivity have they notice
based on antigenic prediction ace -
binding region is a weak antigenic
determinant
wait so the DNA vaccine actually works
this some guys trying to make an open
source open vaccine yeah these guys I
tried to donate some Bitcoin to them but
they used to seg would address bitcoin
went through all right stop spamming my
immunology notes from Union I don't
think you want me to open those on the
stream the DNA vaccines were never
approved please watch this now right
make you a mod please
now-now-now whose trolling next-next
trolls you know we're gonna
martial law in the chat man that's
difficult so wait when the mice and
monkeys for what's that a Dino viral
delivery vaccine containing expressible
full length of the spike gene anti h2
binding region activity was combination
is to find a new genetic determination
and maybe uses an antigen for SARS
vaccination I mean yeah this is
basically what these guys were saying
and like it makes a lot of sense that
they had
let's see are they
Express a modified form of the spiked
protein
modifications to increase its stability
if you're in cleavage site let's
understand I'm sure I google this
yesterday and I just forget
what is urine now oh it's a ubiquitous
what - so many words we may want to
consider mutating this site
oh it's modified isn't it attenuate you
know it can't penetrate the
transmembrane proteins but it's
recognized as an antigen okay that makes
sense yeah yeah the feelings are not a
host side okay yeah I'm sure you've got
something your body produces it's not in
the thing it's just weird that it's at
ended up talking about attenuation
they're talking about stabilities right
like I mean I guess you wouldn't want
all these spike proteins binding to your
a sites but yeah the whole sphere
includes the spike yeah I know it's yeah
okay so that makes that so it's a fury
and cleavage aside but oh interesting so
we should actually be able to find that
oh that's a good open question find
Puran we in spiked glycoprotein you know
these things could just be called like
any wizard magic and it's all saying man
you're just manipulating symbols you
know
oh yeah you're either making a claim
about where it is PRR eh
so they're saying actually that oh let's
test that so if you wrote some code that
is to get this bike leg over to you from
source no module named data yes we're
just gonna restart and then of course
there are spy micro progeny we just do
Corona so something like approaching
night so these are the two so they're
saying it's a PR RA let's do so the fury
oh look at that cleavage site can i
cleave this one can't cleave this one
look at that quality man look at that
quality you know
this might have been an easy let's try
to understand if this is like a known
thing or did that just come from that
one paper I don't like how all these
papers are talking about in general the
more papers are talking about Cobb -
unless interested why does you know like
why do they even think these are the
same thing why did they align it like
that that it doesn't look aligned to me
all those symbols look wrong Furion text
PRA about that you know this is all
why do they sink
here we go so something like predicted
if you're in substrate and the location
of furin cleavage sites can be predicted
by two bioinformatics methods see they
named stupid terms so if I feed in the
sequence
what are these things raw prediction of
pro protein this seems better the twenty
residue recognition sequence motif is PI
towel open source
no here we go
Tresa fishel gene symbol I think I can
get that
no this one
so the Jean I don't know what a file
file this but maybe okay
Bactria
my friend work for a Chinese company and
you know their big company like billion
dollars and then write stuff in English
occasionally that my friends from
America I like you speaks English you
know and you proofread it and he'd be
like you know this isn't how you write
things and then you know the big boss
was kind of like no no no no no no and
that's why things are released I know
but don't know we all think it's
disgusting monetizing the human disaster
it's disgusting how close are we to
cracking it man let me tell you
something about the ps3 you know the ps3
took me five weeks but iPhone took me 12
no and then like to really finish the
ps3 took another like the ps3 was like a
six month project the iPhone was a
three-month project the first time the
jailbreaks were usually done in about a
week but yeah I mean what this shit's
gonna take 12 weeks man wait you think
we're gonna find a vaccine tomorrow
yeah we just got started you watch my
all my streams
we've put three days into this it's
gonna take a while to hack the
coronavirus guys no I mean if if Cora
knows vaccine is gonna work
get back there get back to that I was
waiting a hacker all a virus or issue of
new stuff we need his alone versus stuff
I know to hack the ps3 when I did the
first iPhone I didn't know the
difference between kernel and user space
I didn't understand that the baseband
was a separate processor I knew what
Idol was but I never really used it
before
yes in the fun folder you have a plug-in
for file one of those
[Music]
yes II like I didn't know no I mean I
learned it that and the like no no the
see I'll say something else to George
Watsky I think phrase this well it's you
see the words I say and they portray me
am a nicest light if only you heard the
typewriter chatter tap tap tapping
through my mind at night so for every
project I've succeeded at there's also
been a lot that I failed at you know I
put a lot of time in my life into trying
to find a collision and sha-1 Oh like a
lot of time like I put months into that
and I know sha-1 gosh I worked on this
stupid Nokia phone for weeks and weeks
and weeks
I wrote a GPU hash cracker to crack
these these Nokia hashes I missed a
stupid RSA exploiting that one that came
out a few months later and then the GPU
thing became a thing and then I use
those GPUs to my Bitcoin and buy drugs
yeah so like not all the projects
succeed
no no if this is gonna be one of the not
succeeds or fails but it'd be pretty
cool you know don't you think I've been
learning a lot of stuff which is really
cool I really like learning you know I'm
gonna see you guys if you don't know I'm
part time Accomando I'm not a not a
comma full time anymore we're profitable
the company is going well well one of
this week this week's not so great um
through the most part were profitable uh
yes I've been you know I've been working
on backspace worked on backspace bed I
didn't promote it to part-time that's
true but yeah so I have some time I
don't know I I kind of like hanging out
on stream and I kind of like talking
it's it's nice stream for the next a
couple of days until I really have to
focus on something and write some real
code
but I mean like also like you know where
is this project going I mean I don't
know where we're learning first that's
the the first step to any to exploit in
any system is don't I still do a lot of
work at comma but you know it's just not
it's not a full-time job anymore you're
hiring too if any of you are interested
no it's a cool place to work like I
think that we're I think that it's like
really gonna track to solving
self-driving cars I don't really I
really feel that way last year but what
am I trying to achieve well the first
thing that you do whenever you're about
to have a system is you have to learn
everything about it when I did the ps3 I
had a wiki that documented everything on
the ps3 for the iPhone I don't think I
had a wiki yet I think I just like the
cool thing about roars engineering this
is like Wikipedia has when you're
looking up something specific from the
iPhone for example it was a binary
called BB updater and BB update or was
it's the thing that updated the baseband
oh man you know I think back I think
back in like how long would it take to
do that iPhone unlock today no time at
all
I worked in uh I was an intern at SpaceX
it's
people work very hard there if people
are very motivated by the mission um oh
just cuz of my skills about the iPhone I
galactic thank you for subscribing
a promoter that drives expression of the
protein what is this website just like
ipfs I would see yeah that's cool
Caesar as a cryptic line that's good at
them they if you have something see
fifty four million
cool
do I think he longs over it it no I
think I don't know why we got derailed
on this topic but I think without him
there wouldn't be a SpaceX and a Tesla
and when I think about what companies
are actually doing anything today to
push the envelope those are the first
two that come to mind I Google and
Facebook have metastasized
I think Yeon's foundational sciences
physics
he's a modernist and I think my
foundational science is information
theory and as disgusting of a term as it
is I'm a postmodernist
no he'll uh knows a lot of physics
doesn't know as much about you know I
keep learning and stuff remember that
time that you know this is why Yvonne
always claims that he's gonna solve
self-driving cars in two years it's a
growth is exponential man boring
companies the dumbest shit
I think boring company is like
neuro-link school but he's not gonna
achieve what he claims with that boring
company know that
what I'm not doing a security shit man
we're doing a security now computer
security has played out and you know
over on my losers today don't do that
shit
computer security look when I did it
like 15 years ago it was cool like
hacking was this like true do you like
reading frakkin stuff today you're going
to DeVry University in getting a degree
in cyber security you know
all right
besides wrong so I'm just gonna use
expresses we learned with plasmids boy
that's spider beard video is very cool
build api's around Corona solutions
there but I'll give it a try what I know
a great API
it's called CSV
a poly a site after the coding sequence
an origin of replication and an
antibiotic resistance gene yeah there
and there in plasmids
it's cool how it works the spider beer
video describes it basically you only
some of your bacteria are gonna take up
the plasmid right and then the bacteria
replicating a replicate the plasmid
hopefully - but you're left with you a
really large percentage of bacteria that
don't have the plasmid and how do you
separate the ones that don't from the
ones that do well your plasmid includes
an antibiotic resistance gene you put
that antibiotic in the solution and then
you're left with only the bacteria
despite protein sequence will need to be
synthesized by a third party so the
spike protein is this many amino acids
maybe cobble together can you synthesize
a whole plasmid thank you fine if I go
to one of these gene synthesis services
how does it does the DNA just come in a
vial oh they do cloning did they put it
in a I mean there should be a service
actually that can give me will be
delivered dry in a circular eyes plasmid
five thousand base pairs all right so I
get five thousand base pairs i I mean
all right well I'm wasting that many on
the stupid spike throw to you and I hope
I can fit that other stuff in you know
we gotta we got to run Packers on our
code man so what's well there's only
gonna cost me like this is gonna cost me
like four grand bros you think I
actually sent these people like the
coronavirus buy protein mixed with like
a couple other plasmid ship it actually
make it for me
I don't need to see all these people's
idea that you know they're gonna do it
well and I'm gonna do it shake and I can
get this strand of e.coli to do the
replication for me yo sick bro I'm
making bacteria work for us we're not
just killing them anymore
you see it used to be we'd fight them
now we just kill them but in the future
bacteria are gonna work for us because
her mother overload the end of it the a
is theirs at the end of everything
apparently I forget exactly why I think
it's because whenever it's copied some
of those a's fall off sometimes it was
like a's at the end of your DNA and
eventually like the a's start to get
eaten up and then you die
yeah telomere that's it is it called
telomere compound structure or region
repetitive nucleotides wait that doesn't
look like a z'
Wow
these books full of words that I don't
know
and no free Giga prep
oh good thing they don't have endotoxins
enough
wait which kid was that a Giga frat kid
Wow
should we start buying some of this
stuff he couldn't get here
we should try some simple stuff first
you know when you start boning stuff you
don't start pulling your first buffer
overflows are in joke programs right so
like yeah we'll make like you know
glowing glowing Easter whatever good
compilers for this and stuff the spider
beer guy seems like he was just sticking
them together but I will you I will
point out that I haven't seen that
project actually get finished get a
thermal cycler and start doing PCR yeah
let's buy thermal cycling does it
remember a good recommendation
genome compiler calm
at gene org why don't if this dream is
better what changed
really they use viral vectors I wait
oh no it's prone to dimerization I
definitely don't want that or do up is
that a good thing
no ooh bad em Kalama plasma sent in
bacteria as agar stab go you ever you
ever those strep throat kids I hear late
and then your oven on the plate
the doctor let me rub it on the plate
once I thought it was cool
well that was crazy that's what they did
back in the day I'm sure they'd never
show that to you now you know what I
mean I mean I've been to the doctor in a
long time boy
when I was a kid I go to the doctor and
didn't want to test to see if I had
strep throat this was sick and they just
they'd stick a swab down it though
and they'd uh rub it on an agar plate
then they put the agar plate in the in
the heater and they had the quick test
in the long test I think the long test
they didn't like put it in a heater or
something cuz some of them like died by
heat or something and then they would
just look at it and be like oh yeah
those bacteria is we're gonna prescribe
you some amoxicillin
this Abdeen site is amazing for learning
these methods oh if I'm conducting
coronavirus research they'll prioritize
my order that's nice of them
I don't think they give you at all for
strep throat them virus of the day oh so
cool it's got a lot of stuff in it
honey base-pairs is that was that base
pairs that amino acids 20 base pairs six
kilobases
all viruses are expensive who are these
people
it's a non-profit plasma
Wow
I can send them plasmids wait I mean I
guess okay these things I guess I think
DNA I guess is Matt's table I can get
CRISPR plasmids stuff I can buy it's an
empty back man if I could just write the
right code you know you have to contact
specific labs you email check my
credential so what I mean credentials
what are my credentials create an
account I'm in the United States
academic I'd say type in institution
huh , a we're not gonna do that now we
can I'm sure we can not seven what do
you mean by institution man
what's an institution so they have did I
have a description of what it is do I
need to buy a thermal cycler first and
then put it in the thing and put a
little sign over it and say you know
which we name it guys
yeah yeah
no no comment as an institution ordering
what is it MTA
they still make it clear to me like what
is a lab verifying the status of your
organization
yeah you guys see I say yeah well just
because we could set up and set up an
organization exactly yeah I think the
lab is a place where I could look
welcome to welcome to my my lab we
conduct experiments research
[Music]
three
I heard about sous-vide okay how do i
sous-vide vrv exe thank you for
subscribing I used to have a vacuum
sealer
he's the smuggle leading to burning them
you know I got my car searched and you
talk I didn't have any weed some
bullshit thought I got searched they
found my vacuum sealer cops like what do
you use this for
if I'd known about sous-vide I would
have said sous-vide there we go um but I
don't have a vacuum sealer anymore
Oh yo guys no real talk though I bought
something today if you do get through my
buyers important to have how am i doing
oh oh oh yeah 99 that's right my labs
very under-equipped
so tomorrow I'm gonna wake up at 7 a.m.
and go to Rite Aid and stand in line to
make sure I get one of the seven
thermometers and the thermometer rations
oh no my oxygen is 99 it's good
no it's percent bro yeah if that goes
below yeah if that goes below 95 it's
time to start worrying I mean the other
thing that I don't have in my house that
I'd like to have okay so it seems like
there's like four stages to coronavirus
there's the asymptomatic stage some
people never get past that there's the
symptoms but they're flu-like and
manageable and your pulse oximeter won't
go below you know it won't go below 95
if it does go below 95 you need oxygen
and then if the oxygen stops working you
need a ventilator I'm not gonna go so
crazy as to buy a ventilator but if I
could buy oxygen I wouldn't mind it I
mean this is no like for stage it's not
stages but it's like you know how far
the virus can progress in each person
right there oxygen balloons know like
let's look in this office of oxygen
concentrator if you get coronavirus you
think you're gonna die you're probably
not gonna die bro
you might but it's unlikely I know the
demographics of my stream
at lunch it works it ever like you know
this this this it seems to affect men
more than women you know more men are
getting infected with it than women and
then you realized that the reason for
this is probably because men don't wash
their hands nearly as well as women your
95 well your program
I mean this is the thing right
treatment low blood oxygen level oh here
we go
I know if I buy an oxygen machine Djuka
me use it all the time
liquid oxygen tank should I get one to
have a fire extinguisher lows by make
sure they're all sold out Wow
that I was looking at those losers the
batteries but here 7-liter
do you hook this thing up with a
two-board can I just have more oxygen in
my house I kind of want one of these
Oh No No
what else do they sell
I get that yeah yeah you gotta buy an
oxygen machine no you want to buy a
mobile wireless charger guys you put
upon oxygen
it'll be here in may after everyone dies
[Laughter]
yo Meza nitrous knob well it's oxygen
you wanna hit
we I mean honestly like I want one of
these not just to save me from
coronavirus but like it delivers air
through a subset well you carry on
working say goodbye to coffee jitters
and unplanned hours is breathing oxygen
bad for
I went to one of those oxygen bars once
when I was hungover in Vegas that's
pretty nice
don't they don't one of the ways like
the cyclist guys cheat is they
wait no no no no no no
so anything to people who's this
no it's sold out everyone had the same
idea they bought all the oxygen ooh one
new oxygen March 27th that's not that
far away you let me see if I'm logged
into my Amazon on this other browser yes
I am to remove those proceed to checkout
whenever it gets here we now have 20
dollars worth of oxygen showing up oh
wait no it's not gonna show up till
April or May
never mind cancel order no no I'm not
waiting for April 27th to May 6th I'm
out item did not arrive on time
all right this really got derailed
I think I think yeah I think I think
we're gonna call it a night
$666 yeah I think we're gonna call it a
night
thank you all for watching tonight's
stream what did we do tonight we went
over some some curves we made a little
bit of progress the reverse engineering
we went on some tangents about oxygen
yeah we didn't really do that much
tonight
maybe we'll stream tomorrow no promises
for stream tomorrow the first stream
starts the strong gets to them the
streams kind of fall off I feel a little
tired why I'm the key man at coronavirus
you know don't like jazz music no no I
cracked piosolver
all right dude we'll do the three minute
Q&A
who's being racist no racism in my
stream that's right don't have plans to
develop a Gita Mabel get to it after
coronavirus fireflies man I was a good
song but I used neuro-link as a first
adopter he'll know how I manage my
passwords I'm going to tell you that I
do tend to programming how do i improve
so fast let me tell you I've been
programming since I was five I don't
know if you call 25 years fast but is
our company thinking about expanding
into bioinformatics No Khamenei I solve
self-driving cars me personally
I'm gonna start a bio lab and then buy
things from gene bank or whatever those
things were no well use red or blue
switches I got the top rate capacitors
and we never talk about keyboards on
here yes I've heard about rocket League
I play rocket League
do you have Asperger's Asperger's I
don't know man you tell me what's my
first program it printed out like pee
pee and poop and stuff and I thought it
was funny I was like before don't it
you know whenever people ask about
adderall cuz I feel like I talk about it
all the time can you kill you guys in
the chat like just respond to the
adderall people with my usual spiel on
adderall how are you an intern give me a
job at common AI or you want to be an
intern in the bio lab well the bio lab
doesn't have any funding stuff sorry
about that
come in and does the best we learned
computational linear algebra what do you
mean by computational linear algebra I
mean like deep water deep why is Elin
saying Coronas a joke I don't think he
said that I think he said coronavirus
panic is
like x4 on a virus panic is dumb
panic is dumb man you know like you like
it like if you're referring to those
people who are like hoarding toilet
paper and stuff like yeah that's dumbest
shit man 12 it was not even an essential
good off the top of your head recite a
line of code will always remember int
main parentheses int arc see char RV
char star RV little thingies close pants
still meditate yeah that take yesterday
no don't be smoking these days man
coronaviruses out there someone really
psyched me out about that what
everyone's gonna buy toilet paper I'm
not gonna be the idiot that doesn't that
does a good point
lots of unpaid internships didn't Obama
make them illegal no I got a right a bot
do I have enough toilet paper I'm not
gonna tell you man motivated about the
future of comma yeah yeah man I'll tell
you getting mod low tacking is to
commercialize nowadays it's true you
know it's not commercialized by oh man
there's a whole wave of bio that's just
gonna be taken out from underneath these
shitty medical organizations you know
think about it man
yeah I was gonna use an example of
something but shouldn't talk about that
but the the things that the open source
world can do and can do so quickly if
everybody at home had DNA printers I
mean we probably would have died from
someone releasing something terrible but
you know we also would probably have a
vaccine by now
right just imagine how many people at
home would be willing if they had
printers to just experiment on
themselves and like try a whole bunch of
different things you know like just
print out a plasma it's print out plasma
it's print out plasmids inject them see
what kind of response you get
it would go horribly for some people but
very quickly we figure out what works
and what doesn't you know
universal health care you mean the
government being in charge man what is
the government in charge of that's good
again don't make me bring that graph up
again but you find that things the
government's involved in like education
and healthcare are terrible and things
that the government really has no say
over at all like TVs are awesome and
things like cars and housing or somewhat
in the middle because the government has
some sales enough software is also
software's also got incredible fire
departments that's true though you do
want the government involved with fire
departments because do I do I give this
example is probably one of the things I
talk about if you had a for-profit fire
department pretty no fires isn't that
hard there aren't even that many fires I
mean you know they'd set up as a
consulting service to prevent fires but
eventually really they're gonna have to
get growth you know they're gonna ship
their quarter-over-quarter growth of the
number of fires they put out and it's
just not gonna be enough fires to go
around so you're gonna get a skunkworks
division this is with the incentive set
you're gonna get a skunkworks division
the arson division right I mean you know
they don't tell their estimate company
but they start the fires Fire Department
goes puts them out and growth goes up
right member the episode in Silicon
Valley when they got the the click farm
you know faking all the clicks it's
awesome division yeah
no health insurance is not exactly the
same you think they're gonna make people
sick that's something that's a little
further fetched there's a lot of people
there's a whole lot more people out
there who will do property damage like
things right and look here's how the
artisan division would work right the
artisan division is not going to go
around burn and we ran to people's
houses down they're not gonna be very
popular they're gonna find somebody who
is a nice fire insurance policy and burn
their house down right there's a whole
lot more people out there willing to do
financial fraud than actually do harm to
another person food deserts already made
people sick
I don't know is that Wiz Zee's food
deserts man people's always talking
about this you know
favorite conspiracy theory infinity is a
scam a fine itust
keep it up they help us all stay calm
thank you thank you I can't help me stay
calm till it's nice and calming we're
destroying people's lives in the global
economy for Less deaths in the annual
flu well so here's the problem with that
you know and I yeah I want to say like
like in my personal life Khamenei is
still shipping out products we're
shipping out products on schedule I
think that it's important while being
safe from coronavirus to keep the
economy going as best you can
I think that yeah I mean I think the
economy is really important but right
now it's less deaths than the annual
flow if if this thing spreads to a huge
percentage of the population it's gonna
be a lot more deaths than the flow and
you can't just say like right now it
hasn't all right all right let's say I
have a car that one out of ten cars you
know randomly jerks a steering wheel and
drives off a bridge right and let's say
I've sold a hundred of those cars you
could be like well yeah but I don't like
you know it only killed ten people man
you know Toyota cars killed like 12,000
well yeah you know you sold as many cars
as Toyota you see the problem the
mortality rate is significantly higher
Taylor and Kim refuting oh is this is
this more that cuz Kanye yo I made that
bitch famous you an anarcho-capitalist I
don't know what that is man you know my
thoughts on Anarchy its P equal to NP I
don't think so but I do think that P
equals B P P all right I'm sorry bqp B
also equals P P P but I think that one
more people accept
don't don't pee dogs trigger me don't
get me started on p-values Ben
I feel about theorem 2.00 opinion will
win the next election I'm not in the
politics man I think Joe Biden has
dementia and then like America is gonna
have to choose between you know a man
with dementia and Trump and like we'll
see what we choose do I think is gonna
win I think we're ever predicted says
love your column ideological be QP x BQ
p equals b QP b keep not be QP our Z
distribution you can go to any doctor
that you willing to wait for it meaning
you don't have to go with the network
for free when do I think coronavirus
will be last week's news I mean what's
gonna happen that's bigger than
coronavirus thank you I tried I feel
calm tonight I didn't feel so calm
yesterday I do not wear Crocs No
I mean when was 911 last week's news
right I mean it's not boy it was
I don't really believe that BCH is a
real Bitcoin I think it's a funny meme I
don't think there's any such thing as
the real Bitcoin that's why it's funny
9/11 was last week's news like seven
weeks after it happened I don't know
about the Hat you know I was there I
lived I lived half an hour from from the
World Trade Center and I set off to
school early you go home and it wouldn't
have thought cable TV back then we had
antenna TV you're trying to TV on
channel 2 works but four or five seven
nine eleven and thirteen don't you know
why George Hotz
don't don't what
I was a stock market crash affected me
to be honest like yeah it was money and
it's all fake anyway you know if we
solved cancer or heart disease do you
think coronavirus would be a real threat
no cancer and heart disease are a much
bigger deal in coronavirus if I had you
know if I get coronavirus I'm not that
scared if I get cancer shit
I'm not talking shit about 9/11 man I'm
not talking shit what I think I'm
talking shit
cancer can't be transmitters yeah no no
I mean I think I think coming back to
the original question like that I think
about that story I told it's not talking
shit I'm more saying like this is just
what made 9/11 extremely real for me I
mean it's weird you know small things
like that
my Evert Maya scared of AI is Ilana I
don't think so
I watched the first episode of the bill
gates thing where do I see myself in 15
years I don't know but I think I got
something to think about like when will
this be old news
we're gonna talk about it for a while
it is a lot there's a lot of you say
like the volatility index of the stock
market's extremely high
yeah now just me that but for longer
someone wants a link you guys do a great
job with us oh yeah that's cool
Oh
why is that little that's the recession
that's coronavirus
well it's good that volatility is going
down
Wow
what happened that
yeah that's I mean that's the financial
crash this is cool
I think Briggs it was actually that big
a deal I also don't think Trump's
election was that big a deal
though the government shutdown
honestly does the government do anything
beside to take our money it's kind of
how I feel I mean if the government
shutdown I mean the Russia government
shutdown and it was kind of okay so yeah
I'm gonna give the power back to the
states yeah that sounds like something
do you think Corona will dip off on us
for asked to have a good 4/20 no these I
think these next two months are gonna be
rough I don't see it might taper out but
the problem is if it tapers out and we
if your tapers out because of the
quarantine measures as soon as we let up
on the quarantine measures it's just
gonna go up again do you think human
response to coronavirus would be
adequate enough when faced with an
actual viral trap I think this is
definitely an actual viral threat I'm
not sure not sure what more your expects
to be fair if this thing had like a 50%
death rate I think everyone would
respond the way more extremely and
actually I think if it had a 50% death
rate it never would have spread right
like you think about it like that you
think about it once things become too
deadly humanity will go to any extreme
to stop them but my age range
Korona 0.2% chance killing right you
know how scared of me I get the disease
a one-month incubation of a person yeah
we'd we'd we'd be under martial law a
minute
what do I think it's gonna stop I think
give it two more months and we're gonna
have a really good eye I think I think
even in a month we're gonna have a good
idea of an answer to that question
oh yeah I should play those games
pandemic and plague and stuff but human
languages yo hablo espanol mas o menos
yo quiero duermo and me clase por que no
your no entiendo mas no hablo rapido I'm
just like who is that guy Marco Rubio or
plague cough I don't know that's not
that's not that's not the game is that
the game what's like pandemic is the
game
this good wasn't reviews it was banned
in China it's got to be good
overwhelmingly positive very positive I
was doing
I don't like show you guys my Steam
account shit
let's do it over here let's play some
play game it's gonna take a long time to
download plaguing of all yes yes dad to
Cart purchase for myself
they must have created esteem yeah yeah
yeah sweet
alright we're downloading plague Inc
yo look we're playing games like a
little horsey keystrokes no
all right my mouse pose
autopsy's me my mouth furnace there we
go
Oh create my very own fake news story
alright let's go wait let me first see
can I make the resolution bigger
[Music]
or I have to unlock a virus okay we'll
play it with bacteria oh damn this is
[Laughter]
I'm a new player let's play it on casual
name my plane SARS no it's a bacteria we
got a name of a bacterial polio b2 let's
go hang on I'll make me smaller so you
guys can see the whole game casual is
really easy is it too easy select a
country to begin my play well we know
what country were to City oh good I love
that they haven't grounded the planes
yeah
ah
all right what can I do well look at
those hot spots oh no no no I need to
click there I'm gonna minimize this so
it doesn't keep doing this okay well
good I think we guys have spread to
Mongolia
you control the plague indirectly by
evolving it here we go
alright alright
[Music]
blood took blood of poor beauties
insects
oh that sounds nice yeah oh yeah if I
just increase the infectivity we'll get
everybody severity doesn't even have to
be too bad I thought that we want
severity for goals is our goals just to
infect everyone or to kill them all
[Music]
it comes by us at all you're on the
wrong team bro
[Music]
okay why does this affect me
see what the symptoms are
oh yeah I like that yeah yeah let's make
people unable to sleep Oh
[Music]
hypoxia believes it is bacterial we
should really spend some time on
antibiotic resistance
yeah business is usual no we got to shut
this down believe they ban this Aegina I
love that we live in a free country guys
upper-right oh I can increase the speed
oh I see
Oh people are being infected faster and
faster okay wait just time stop when I
do that now we get we gotta make it more
effective yeah
oh yeah spread to Russia look at that
that's a lot of infected people killing
anybody not oh no aid initiative
there we go yeah that'll get those more
countries
oh yeah
sounds annoying
[Music]
who more infectious than TV yes is down
people are gonna start to respond to
this fast now okay all right looks like
a lot of the world that's pretty good
sweet they haven't grounded anything yet
oh yeah you got on a plane that was a
dumb choice birds insects Oh air that
sounds good
mm that's a good point we need 12 TN
okay I gotta get a few more and then
we're gonna buy that yeah that's right
look we're seeing all that sort of
harmless disease Oh harmless you say
perfect
that sounds nice
and you I just my question kind of is if
I then change the symptoms research
priority hello God perfect
there's not enough dead people though
again we got to increase the number then
people how do we do that
[Music]
Oh No let me shut down the borders
fatal source of gangrene yeah but if
people die aren't they gonna do more
research yeah what else makes it more
deadly oh yeah that's good
like people looking for a cure now let's
pause while we figure out how to make
sure that doesn't happen
yeah that's right slow down your
research
[Music]
when are they gonna find it - uh-oh that
doesn't seem good
[Music]
all right we haven't gotten Africa yeah
let's get Africa
[Music]
what's gonna make it spread in Africa
livestock yeah
[Music]
or insects that always get some in
Africa
[Music]
extraordinary mutation packs what was
Morocco hard Algeria
I think that's gg
there's definitely a way to lose this
game I just played it on easy mode well
that's a brutal game so glad I don't
live in China where we have to know
we're in America where we have free
speech you can play caves like that wait
I haven't gotten everybody yet any more
symptoms yeah
those last million aren't gonna find the
cure
[Music]
pretty cool playin artist all right all
right all right play hard all right I
got you
all right you know what yeah yeah that's
that's a good idea
well we'll end the stream on a hopeful
note where I lose that's that's a good
idea
plays don't always win sometime Humanity
trials it's a new mode to save the world
by popular demand
oh and normal or higher door lock let's
see the scenarios
huh
I'm just play on hard
Kove it 60 all right we'll start this
one in the USA
I like it surviving in water
two infected can I lose before they even
like spread it at all three sweet
[Music]
hmm
you'll get him on birds
[Music]
touchdown mine
well
[Music]
the first ideas to spend on an activity
our budget people streaming us
all right rats and sold yeah get the
city dwellers man Oh coughing senator
sweet
level two hypetrain yo get this high
train goin less win mega brutal
this pathogen kind of sucks why is
everybody like washing their hands all
right should we upgrade for double rats
bird it's not enough let's get Birds
fifteen VNA points
this games actually being extremely
generous to me this thing would have
died out a long time ago like this it's
a bacteria and you can have like a deep
reservoir of it or something
what do I do
[Music]
it's the problem is time you know
never got to get the birds
[Music]
but it's not even spreading in the US
you know why don't I pick a less
developed country
we still the same five people
is this just just brutish take forever
about five people
strong dry witness
I need more transmission yeah yeah well
I don't I only have four DNA points of
great abilities think so
anymore transmission I think I upgraded
a lot of these try livestock or we can
try to get one of these
[Music]
where are we right now there's a fairly
rural areas of America
[Music]
this disease is boring
yeah weird aiming no 3,400 maybe in
Ethiopia on the tsunami Oh
the tsunami killed him well I'm losing
to a tsunami
alright alright eight people all right
no six people never mind
Mexico that's a good strategy
I like the Mexico strategy what we'll
spread it to Mexico
alright let's save up for that insect
Mexico closed its borders over ten
diseases no they didn't oh you mean IRL
yeah IRL I think they did the irony
do we save up for the super rats
go into the death toll numbers
yeah I can devolve but I barely get any
points for it it seems like you just
gotta like be patient wait for those
things to pop up
I can't tonight put rats I think I can
program
[Music]
bird seems like a good deal me 22
Oh devolve all symptoms okay
[Music]
but it costs money to devolve I don't
even get it back
I just spent money on devolving not all
the ones that gave you in fact imitating
you get small amounts back no it looks
like I just spent things and now I have
less infectivity you know what ultra
brutal wins guys ultra brutal wins
you know humanity wins that's that's a
pleasant note with which to end
tonight's stream on maybe I'll see you
again tomorrow but probably no I I
probably let stream again Wednesday no
no more Q&A ready to Q&A it's bedtime
good night everybody thank you all for
watching
we are gaming channel a Christian
channel we spread love and everybody
subscribed to me so we can spread money
and buy spread money I mean spread money
you know what I mean I checked my twitch
I'm like damn I'm making money I should
stream more but then I remember that I
don't do it for the money I do it for
the love